Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- C, 1851-2005; 3
  - Champagne, Jane, Undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Champagne, Kevin, Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Chan, Wing Ming, Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Chandra, Uday, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Chang, Jane C., Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Chang, Julius S., Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Chang, Shirley, Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Chapel House, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Chapman, David W., Undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Chapman, Dennis, Undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Chapman, Sara, Undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Charnews, Joan, Undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Chartock, Alan, Undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Chatterton, Robert G., Undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Chen, Chan-Fu, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Chen, Kuan I., Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chen, Yu-Hui, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chen, Yu-Shih, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cheng, Leida, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cheng, Pei-Kai, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cheng, Roger, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cheng, Roger J., Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chepaitis, Barbara, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chernaivsky, Michael, 1972 August 20-1973 June (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cherubini, Jon, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chessin, Henry, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chesin, Sorrel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chesin, Sorrel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chi, Benjamin Exner, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Childers, Wesley J., 1941-1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Childs, John L., Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Childs, Lindsay N., Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Childs, Lindsay N., Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Childs, Lindsay N., Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Chisholm, Michael E., Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chisolm, S.W., Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Chittur, Sridar, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chiuchiolo, Nicholas, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chou, Chien-Fu, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Chow, Julian, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Christenson, Elia H., Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Christakis, Michael N., Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Christianson, Scott, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Christie, Leona, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Christensen, Edward, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Christodulu, Kristin, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Christoff, Patrick L., Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Chui, Sin-Tat, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Chun, Elsie, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Chung, Ling, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Church, Thomas W., Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chylek, Peter, Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Cimini, Delores, Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Ciompi, Arturo, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Cioppa, Anne, Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Cipperly, Joan, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Cipriano, Ramon J., Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Claiborne, Nancy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Clark, Richard M., Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Clarkin, William H., Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Clas, Carol Ann, Undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Clausen, Ralph G., Undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Clogston, A.M., Undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Closson, William, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Clyman, Toby W., Undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Cobane, Edith M., Undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Coburn, Judy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Cochran, David H., 1828-1909 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Cochran, John C., Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Cochrane, James, Undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Cockrell, Findlay, Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Cockrell, Findlay, Undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Cocks, Peter, Undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Cocks, Peter G., Undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Cody, Evelyn, Undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Cody, Michael, Undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Coe, Richard (Rick) S., Undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Coffey, Martin J., Undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Coffey, Martin J., Undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Cognon, Jacques, Undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Coco, Raymond P., Undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Cohen, Donald L., Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Fred, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, Fred, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Tom, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cohon, Rachel, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Colby, Frances L., Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Colello, Joseph, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Colemn, Marion Moore, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Colfer, Carmelinda, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Collier, Carolin, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Collier, Mary Beth, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Collier, Naon D., Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Collier, Naon D., Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Collins, Arthur N., Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Collins, Evan R., 1984 May 19 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Collins, Jack B., Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Collins, James, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Collins, Jefferey L., Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Collins, Mark S., Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Collins, Mary, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Colman, Charles Wilson, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Colpitts, Phyllis A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Colquhoun, William R., Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Comproski, Kimberly, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Conaway, O.B., Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Conboy, Regina, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Condon, William, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Conklin, Douglas, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Conley. Thomas N., Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Connelly, Joseph P., Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Connophy, Peter F., Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Conway, John, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Cook, Earl, Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Cooper, Frank, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Cooper, Philip J., Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Cooper, Philip J., Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Cooren, Francois, Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Corbett, Diane, Undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Corbett, James W., Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Corbin, Alice, Undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Cornet, Florencia, Undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Corning, Erastus, Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Cornish, Alicia R., Undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Corso, Michael, Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Cotton, William R., Undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Courington, Geri, Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Countermine, William A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Covington, Sim, Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Cowan, L. Gray, Undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Cowley, Edward, Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Cowling, Vincent F., Undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Cowling, Vincent J., Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Cox, George, Undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Craig, Hardin, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Craig, Randall T., Undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Craighead, John J., Undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Creegan, Robert, Undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Cresswell, Anthony M., Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Croasdale, Caroline, Undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Cromack, Theodore, Undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Cross, Robert, Undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Crowley, James, Undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Crowley, James A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Crull, Harry Edward, 1965-1972 April 25 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Cruz, Jose, Undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Cue, Nelson, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Cully, Thomas, Undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Cully, Thomas, Undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Cummings John Carey, Undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Cummings, Paul A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Cummings-Danson, Gail, Undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Cundy, Donald, Undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Cunninghan, Richard P., Undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Cunningham, Veronica, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Cupoli, Ed, Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Curry, Deborah, 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Curtis, Thomas E, Undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Curtis, Thomas E, Undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Cushman, Donald P., Undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Cusick, Roger, Undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Cutler, Gary, Undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Cutler, Gary, Undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Cuttler, Brian, Undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Czapski, Ulrich, Undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
- D, 1851-2005; 4
  - Dabrowski, Romuald, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - D'ambra, Thomas, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - D'Andrea, Frank, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Daims, Diva Barachini, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dale, Mark, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Daly, Lawrence Henry, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Dalton, Mark, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - D'Amello, Joseph, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Damhof, Sandra, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dandridge, Thomas C., Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Danese, Gino, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Daniel, Betty C., Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Daniel, Charles E., Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Daniels, Mina H., Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Daniels, Thomas, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Danielson, Lucig, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Dapo, Donald, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Darbyshire, Sue, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Das, Tara P., Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Dascher, Alfred, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Dascal, Neal, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - D'attilo, Michael, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Davidson, Justine A., Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Davidowicz, Lucy, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Davis, Edward D., Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Davis, Liane, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Davis, Lydia, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Davis, Phillip, Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Dawes, Sharon, Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Day, Stephen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Dean, D.E., Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Deane, Glenn, Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Dear, Gary, Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Dearstyne, Bruce William, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - DeBlasi, Anthony, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Decker, Sidney, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Decker, Walter Cornell, Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Dedrick, Blanchard, Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - deGonzague, Arleen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Dehais, Richard J., Undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Deiber, Gwen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Deininger, Richard C., Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - De La Foret, Peggy, Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - DeLaMater, Christine, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - DeLamater, Claudette R., Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Delano, John, Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Delano, John, Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - D'elia, Christopher, Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Dehong, Dennis, Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Delong, Stephen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Delio, Vincent, Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - DelAanto, John H., Undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Deluca, Nicholas, Undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Demacario, Everly Conway, Undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Dembowski, Frederick L., Undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Demerjian, Kenneth L., Undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - DeMeo, Joseph, Undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Debeneaux, Gregory, Undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Dennis, Livia, Undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Dennis, Margaret A., Undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Denton, Nancy, Undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - De Pasquale, Brian, Undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Derrick, Virginia J., Undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Derrick, William, Undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Derringh, Edward, Undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - DeSantis, Deiedre, Undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - DeSantis, Deiedre, Undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Desfosses, Helen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Desfosses, Helen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - De Sole, Gloria, Undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Dunn, Daniel, Undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Devane, Mary Anne, Undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Dewey, John F., Undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Dewey, John N., Undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Dewitt-Parker, Joyce, Undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Diamond, William M., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Dickey, James M., Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Dickinson, Joanne, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Didier, Maureen C., Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - DiDionna, Michelle, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Dieffenback, Bruce, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Digiorgio, Diane, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Dillon, Harold Joseph, 1965-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Dineen, Richard, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Dinovo, Robert, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dirocco-Ruskin, Valerie, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - DiSteffano, Jacqeline S., Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - DoBell, Howard, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Dobson, Michael W., Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Docksai, Ronald F., Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Doellefeld, James Patrick, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Doellefeld, Steven F., Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Doherty, Marijo (also Norman Bauman), Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Dolan, Donna R., Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Doll, Carol A., Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Doman, Mary Gay, Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Domaracki, Jane, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Donahue, John, Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Donley, Donald T., Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Donovan, Robert Alan, Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Donovan, Robert, Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Doolen, Kevin, Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Dorfman, Debrah, Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Doty, David, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Dougherty, Mary Jo, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Douglas, Gertrude E., Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Douglas, James, Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Downey, Shirley, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Dowse, Patricia, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Doyle, Daniel E., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Doyle, Kmberly, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Dozier, Cheryl, Undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Drescher, Nuala McGann, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Dressner, Richard B., Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Drewer, Lois, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Driscoll, E. Gallagher, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Drotar, David Lee, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Bangert-Drowns, Robert L., Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Duarte, Francisco, Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Duch, Raymond, Undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Duchessi, Peter J., Undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Dudek, Bruce C., Undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Dudek, Mairin E., Undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Dudo, Peter J., Undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Duffee, David E., Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Dukes, Jerome E., Undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Dulak, Norman C., Undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Dulay, Heidi, Undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Dumbleton, William A., Undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Dunn, Anita, Undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Dunsmore, Lai Lonnie, Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Dunz, Karl, Undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Dupuis, Barbara, Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Dutkiewicz, Vincent, Undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Dutta, Savarav, Undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Duval-Spillane, Pat, Undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Dwyer, Catharine M., Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Dwyer, Catharine M., Undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Dwyer, John M., Undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Dwyer, Thomas, Undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Dyksta, Robert, Undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
- E, 1851-2005; 5
  - Eadon, George, Undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Eames, Harriet, Undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Earl, Theodore R., Undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Earleywine, Mitchell, Undated (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Ebert, Teresa L., Undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Eccelston, Ava, Undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Eckstein, Jerome, Undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Eckstein, Jerome, Undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Edleman, Martin, Undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Edleman, Martin, Undated (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Edleman, Robert, Undated (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Edleson, Ivan, Undated (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Edleson, Ivan, Undated (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Edelson, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Edelstein, Philip, Undated (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Edoho, Edoho Bassey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Edwards, Charles, Undated (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Edwards, Charles, Undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Edwards, David L., Undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Edwards, Richard L., Undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Egelston, Martha Albright, 1929-1973 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Egelston, Richard, Undated (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Eisenberger, Robert, Undated (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Ekrich, Arthur A., Undated (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Elam, Helen, Undated (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Elbow, Matthew H., Undated (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Elk, Roy, Undated (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Elkin, Dennis, Undated (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Ellinwood, Dewitt, Undated (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Ellinwood Jr., Dewitt Clinton, Undated (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Ellis, Beverly, Undated (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Ellis, Clifford, Undated (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Ellis, Martin H., Undated (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Ellis, Michael, Undated (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Ellis, G.Randall, Undated (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Ellis, Randall, Undated (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Ellis, Richard D., Undated (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Elliston, Frederick, Undated (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Else, Meinda Sue (Ross), Undated (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Elter, John F., Undated (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Emerson, Patricia R., Undated (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Emery, James, Undated (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Empie, KarenEngstron, Mary J., Undated (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Emrich, Robert L., Undated (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Endicott, William, Undated (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Ennis, Paula, Undated (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Ennis, Paula, Undated (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Ensel, Walter M., Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Eparo, Philip, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Erie, Stephen P., Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Erkes, Joseph, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Erlich, Frederick, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Eson, Morris, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Esperson, James P., Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Esposito, Wayne, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Estey, Charles G., Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Etcheverry, Roland, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ether, John A., Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Etheredge, Lloyd S., Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Eubanks, Virginia, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Evans, Aden, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Evans, Carol N., Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Evans, Nancy, 1997 July 30 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Evans, Susan T., Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Ezquerra de Alvar, Elena, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
- F, 1851-2005; 6
  - Fachard, Denis, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Fadale, LaVerne, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Faerman, Sue, Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fahey, Valerie, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Fairbank, Roswell Evan, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Fairbanks, Robert M., Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Fairbanks, Robert M., Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Falbe, Cecilia, Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Falconer, Raymond E., Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Falk, Dean, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Falk, Dean, Undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Falk, Dean, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Falls, Douglas L., Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Fama, Michael M., Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Fancher, Michael M., Undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Farina, Chris, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Farley, John J., Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Farmer, J. Walter, 1928-1989 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Farnworth, Margaret, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Farnsworth, Alton U, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Farr, Daniel, Undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Farrell, Cathy, Undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Farrell, Hazel, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Farrell, Lawrence, Undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Farrell, Laurence, 1903-1989 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Farrell, Margaret A., Undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Faureau, Donald, Undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Faureau, Donald, Undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Federighi, Francis D., Undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Fee, Ruth F., Undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Feeney, JoAnne, Undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Feeser, Patricia, Undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Feister, William J., Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Feldman, Laurie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Feldman, Liza, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Feldman, Jerry, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Felson, Richard Barnet, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Felter, Catherine, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Feltsman, Vladmir, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Femminella, Francis, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Fenlon, Mark W., Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Fenner, Frank, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Fenton, William N., Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ferdman, Bernardo, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Ferguson, Henry, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Ferlo, Patrick, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Fernandez, Dulce, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Fernandez, Frank L., Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Fernandez, Xavier, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ferrara, Donna, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ferretti, Lisa A., Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Fessler, Susanna, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Fetrow, Jacqelyn, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Fetterly, Judith, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Fetterly, Judith, Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Fields, Emmett, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Fields, Lanny, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Fieldsteel, Adam, Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Fiess, Mary, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Figge, James, Undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Fillipone, Julia, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Finder, Morris, Undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Finet, Julia, Undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Fink, Robert Orwill, Undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Finkelstein, Alfred P., Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Finnegan, Daniel, Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Fischer, Philip J., Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Fischer, Sandra K., Undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Fischer, Steve, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Fisher, Charles G., Undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Fisher, Charles L., Undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Fisher, Ingrid, Undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Fisher, Patricia A.P., Undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Fiser, Webb Sackett, Undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Fishman, Harvey M., Undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Fisk, John, Undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Fitch, Martha, Undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Fitzdam, Deb, Undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Fitzgerald, Edward F., Undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Fitzjarrold, David, Undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Flanagan, Timothy J., Undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Flanagan, Timothy J., Undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Flanners, Mary C., Undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Flannery, Daniel, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Fleischer, Robert L., Undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Fleischner, Jennifer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Fleitman, Jacob, Undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Fleming, James T., Undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Flierl, Howard H., 1948-1993 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Foderingham-Herard, Undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Foderingham, Joan, Undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Foderingham, Winsome, Undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Fogelman, Martin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Foley, Dennis P., Undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Fonda, Carol A., Undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Fonseca, John R., Undated (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Fonseca, John R., Undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Foote, Allan D., Undated (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Foote, Eleanor, Undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Forcino, Ana, Undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Ford, Robert, Undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Ford, Robert, Undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Fordham, Ben, Undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Forer, Raymond, Undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Forer, Raymond, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)